aboutourwork.com 2012-11-15

# Company Profiles | Business Networking | Small Business Connection Network | AboutOurWork

## Privacy Policy

_This Privacy Policy is effective June 1, 2011_

AboutOurWork.com (AOW, LLC) is a Limited Liability Corporation based in Columbus, OH.

AboutOurWork.com is committed to protecting the privacy of your information. This Privacy Statement describes AboutOurWork.com’s Web site privacy practices.

If you have any questions or concerns, please email us immediately at privacy@aboutourwork.com.

### Security Statement

At AboutOurWork.com, we respect your privacy. Your information is safe here, with no legal language that can be misconstrued. This is foremost in our thinking and the way we do business.

AboutOurWork.com uses the information you provide us to help personalize your online experience at AboutOurWork.com. We only use your name and email address to send you News or Updates. We will never give or sell your user information or email address to anyone without your consent.

### Email Privacy Matters

We use your email address only to send you information and updates about AboutOurWork.com. You can unsubscribe at any time you wish to be taken off the AboutOurWork.com emailing list.

### Cookies and Your Computer

Like most websites, we use “cookie” technology. A cookie is a very small text file that a website can save onto your computer’s hard disk to store your information and settings. When you log on, the cookie tells us whether you have visited us before or are a new visitor. It doesn’t track any personal information, give us the means to contact you, extract information from your computer or deliver viruses. Furthermore, your address or credit card information is never stored in a cookie. Cookies are simply the most efficient way for us to be able to offer you an enjoyable online experience. We do not share your cookie information with any other entities.

### Disclosure of Personal Information

Any information you provide to us at this site when you establish or update an account, enter a contest, or request information (i.e. name, address, email address, telephone number and credit card information), is maintained in private files on our secure Web server and our internal systems. This information is used to enable AboutOurWork.com to deliver services, products and information to you.

To ensure compliance with federal law, AboutOurWork.com does not maintain information provided by children under the age of 16. If you are visiting AboutOurWork.com from a location outside of the U.S., your connection will be through and to servers located in the U.S.

### Links

For your convenience, our Website may contain links to other sites. AboutOurWork.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites.

### Security

AboutOurWork.com believes in providing a safe and secure experience for all of our users. We provide stringent and effective security measures on our Website.

### Third-Party Ad-Servers

We DO NOT use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. AboutOurWork does not share your information with any Third Parties or advertising companies.

### Links to Social Services / Social Signups

We use Social Connectors such as Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn & Yelp for three purposes only:

  1. To allow our users to link their Business Profile to the Social Services that they own and manage
  2. To allow our users to share news, updates or information about themselves or AboutOurWork.com
  3. To provide a positive overall experience for our users

This Privacy Policy may be updated or revised from time to time.
